timetravels.fi 2016-07-05

# Timetravels Ltd. Privacy_policy

## General

Your privacy is important to us. We know that you care about how information about you is used. We want to share with you the Internet policies and practices we have adopted with respect to our site to protect your privacy so that you feel confident about how we handle the personal information you entrust to us online.

While we do not plan to modify our policies very often, it is always advisable to double-check when you visit our site to be sure that you have read and agree with our most current privacy policy statement. Any change in our privacy policy will be prospective only. We will not make any changes that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so.

The content on our site may include a photo gallery, message boards, surveys, sweepstakes, and contests. We hope that you enjoy the aikamatkat.fi site and will come back often to visit.

## Collection

We only collect personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone numbers, passport , insurance details, demographic information (region/country from), interests, taste or preference information, and the like, when voluntarily submitted by a visitor. Visitors may choose to submit personal information to enter contests, to obtain information or submit a comment, to register for a loyalty program or to place a travel availability request.

## Use of Information & Disclosure

Providing personal information is up to you, our visitor. We will collect personally identifiable information provided by you to notify you of results, to e-mail you with updates and news, to respond to your questions, comments or travel requests, to send out brochures and other information on our products and services, and to enter you in contests. We ask visitors providing e-mail addresses to let us know if they would like further information or updates from our site; only those who request it will receive follow-up e-mail or other communications from us. We will never sell or give the personal information that you voluntarily provide us to any third party, other than to: (a) affiliated entities of Aikamatkat Oy - Timetravels Ltd., (b) service providers who provide support services to us with respect to the site, (c) business partners as described below, and (d) purchasers of all or a part of the Aikamatkat Oy - Timetravels Ltd. business provided that such third party agrees to abide by the privacy policies stated in this statement. It is used solely by us, our agents, affiliates, services providers and business partners to respond to your requests and to better serve you.

We extend these privacy policies to our business relationships. We expect the companies within The Travel Corporation organization and those we select as our service providers and business partners to honor our privacy policies in the handling of customer personal information. These businesses include companies that (a) assist us in providing products and services to our customers, including travel agencies; (b) supply us with information for identifying or evaluating prospective customers; (c) enhance, support and maintain our site; or (d) are given the opportunity to send mailings to approved Aikamatkat Oy - Timetravels Ltd. customer lists. In selecting business partners, Aikamatkat Oy - Timetravels Ltd. considers the accuracy and quality of the data they provide, how they respond to consumer complaints and whether or not they provide opt-out choices for those whose information they process.

## Opt-Out

We also offer visitors an “opt-out” option at any time they wish to cease receiving e-mails or other information from us. If you initially decide to receive information from us but at a later date wish to remove your information from our database, you can do so by sending an email to aikamatkat@aikamatkat.fior by calling us (and mention that you have an opt-out request related to the Aikamatkat Oy - Timetravels Ltd. website).

## "Cookies" and Other Web Technologies

We use “cookie” technology and IP addresses only to obtain non-personal information from online visitors to provide them with the best possible personalized on-line experience. To do this we do keep track of the type of browser (e.g., Internet Explorer, Netscape) and operating system (e.g., Windows, Macintosh) used by the visitor, and the domain name of the visitor’s Internet service provider. We also track the total number of visitors to our site in an aggregate form to allow us to update and improve our site; personally identifiable information is not extracted in this process. This helps us keep our site fresh and interesting to our visitors. Cookie technology also helps us deliver content tailored to a visitor’s interests. You may disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do disable cookies, we may be unable to optimize your visit to our site and you may experience some errors.

## Message Boards & Photo Galleries

We may offer message boards and photo galleries for our customers’ enjoyment. As we are sure you are aware, anything you post online is available for the world to see. We make no representations and undertake no obligations as to information you voluntarily post. By posting a message on our site or sending in photos for our photo gallery, you understand it becomes public domain and therefore may be used by Aikamatkat Oy - Timetravels Ltd. for marketing purposes without any compensation required to be paid to you.

## Safeguards

We have instituted safeguards to check that our internal procedures meet our privacy policy standards. We also use our commercially reasonable efforts to be sure that third parties who work with us agree to protect personal information that they must access in order to serve our site and our visitors.

## Links To Other Sites

We rarely offer links to other sites, but when we do, we try to link only with partner sites that share our values. Nevertheless, we are not responsible for the content or information collection policies of other sites including any links from traveler homepages posted on the message boards. If you visit another site, you should first review their privacy and other policies before providing any of your personal information.

## Other Information and Governing Law

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any legal investigation.

## Questions

If you would like us to update, change, or delete information we have about you (subject to any applicable legal exceptions) or have questions about our privacy policy, please send an e-mail to aikamatkat@aikamatkat.fi We have offices worldwide that correspond with our users, so please be very specific about your query.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

From time to time it may be necessary for Aikamatkat Oy - Timetravels Ltd. to amend or make revisions to this Privacy Policy, which amendments may also apply to your personal information collected under a previous version of this Policy. Aikamatkat Oy - Timetravels Ltd. reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. If we make a change to the Policy, the revised version will be posted on our website.
